weightloss.com.au 2007-12-11

# Privacy Policy of Weightloss.com.au - Australia's premier weight loss website

The weightloss.com.au Privacy Policy.

Your privacy is important to us. That's why we invest in some of the latest security systems and commit to maintaining industry standards relating to your privacy.

It is important that you fully understand the way we obtain and use your personal information and also the limited circumstances in which we may disclose it. This privacy statement details the information we gather, how we may use it, and how you can correct or change it if necessary.

Our web site has areas where you can provide personal information to identify yourself or the company you represent. We have developed this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and practices regarding such information.

This document is the Privacy Policy of Ultimate Weightloss. It relates to the web pages and services available at Ultimate Weightloss Sites, including www.weightloss.com.au. 

Information Collection and Use.

Ultimate Weightloss is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Ultimate Weightloss collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Online Enquiry Forms.**

In order to submit an enquiry form, you are required to provide your contact details (name and email address). This information is used to contact you only about the services on our site that you have expressed interest in.

**Opt-In or Opt-Out.**

It is our anti-spamming policy that as much as we'd love to send you helpful information to assist with your weight loss needs; we simply do not unless you tell us to, through the use of an opt-in check box.

You are able to opt-out of receiving communications from the site by checking the unsubscribe option of the Newsletter page along with your email confirmation.

**Newsletter.**

At some points on our site we provide an opt-in option that you can decidedly check if you'd like to request periodic issues of our popular Weightloss Newsletter. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

You can choose to unsubscribe at any time to our Newsletter either by using the unsubscribe links detailed in the Weightloss Newsletter, or by typing your email address and checking the unsubscribe option of the Newsletter page. 

**Credit Card Information.**

Your credit card number will only be used to charge you for the products and services which you buy or subscribe to.

**Communication.**

You can expect email from us in response to:

  * Solicited email enquiries. We like to think that we are a responsible business and therefore promptly respond to enquiries, comments, and any other feedback.

  * Newsletters. By checking the opt-in box on our contact page or typing your email address and subscribing in the newsletter window clearly interprets your consent to receive newsletters. Newsletters are issued once every month.

  * Message board response notices. You will be posted an email indicating when someone has responded to your message board posting. Upon use of our message board, you are granted the choice to opt-in for this reply service by checking the opt-in box.

If you believe that you are a recipient of any other information not specified above which may or may not be interpreted as spam mail, please email security@weightloss.com.au immediately.

**Log Files.**

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are NOT linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing information.**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our clients, content providers, partners and advertisers. This information is NOT linked to any personal data that can identify you as an individual person, nor do we distribute or sell personally identifiable information to third parties like direct marketers.

**Hyper Links.**

Naturally, this web site contains links to other sites. Ultimate Weightloss is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites. We encourage our users to read [if available] the privacy statements of each web site that collects personally identifiable information as this privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

**Use of Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards.**

When disclosing personally identifiable information online through Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards the information is considered submitted public information. So, when posting public information you are at risk of receiving unsolicited email and therefore we urge you to be extra careful and to use discretion when disclosing information online, especially your email address.

**Security.**

The open nature of the Internet means no data transmission can be guaranteed 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from our online products or services. Therefore these activities are conducted at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we will use our best efforts to ensure its security. 

**Respecting the rights of others.**

In reference to any weightloss.com.au forum you agree not to post, transmit, distribute or link to content that is unlawful, harassing, abusive, threatening, harmful, indecent, obscene, tortuous, libellous, defamatory, invasive of one's privacy or otherwise liable to be viewed as objectionable or threatening physical harm to any person or group.

**Correcting and updating your details.**

The information we receive from you is kept in a secure environment accessed only by authorised Ultimate Weightloss staff and service providers.

You have access to the personal information you provide to us and you can easily update that information.

Access to your personal information can be gained from the administration area and you'll need your username and password in order to modify your personal details. 

**Contact us.**

If you have any questions about this policy statement, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings with Ultimate Weightloss, please contact us Email: [scott@weightloss.com.au](mailto:scott@weightloss.com.au)

Click here to contact us

Thank you for visiting weightloss.com.au.
